ID,post,class,target,implied_statement,implicit_class,extra_implicit_class,tags
399886440588247041,"  "" : jewish harvard professor noel ignatiev wants to abolish the white race via #wr "" "" """,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are oppressors,white_grievance,,"[{'jewish': 'MISC'}, {'harvard': 'ORG'}, {'noel ignatiev': 'PER'}]"
929901925100937216," b.higher education is a part of european culture  that was imported to other continents  although the asian culture pressures their people to aim to be the best at everything ( hence all the stereotypical jokes )  in asian culture  "" studying is everything "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'european': 'MISC'}, {'asian': 'MISC'}, {'asian': 'MISC'}]"
728678509497954304," has a problem with  "" the whites "" "" and "" "" the christians . "" "" go ahead  you are free to say it now ! """,not_hate,,,,,[{'christians': 'MISC'}]
625688620444180481," is yasir qadhi a hate preacher for calling christians  "" filthy "" "" ? - james white refutes robert spencer """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'yasir qadhi': 'PER'}, {'christians': 'MISC'}, {'james white': 'PER'}, {'robert spencer': 'PER'}]"
441089979322597376," rt  "" : how three million germans mass murdered after destruction of the reich ; via "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'germans': 'MISC'}, {'reich': 'LOC'}]"
331067715689263105," rt  "" we were murdered graffiti in synagogues "" "" : i recently watched a video of an older german documentary on jews "" "" ... """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'german': 'MISC'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}]"
755109998770921473," rt : tune in today's jmt for my interview w / robert spencer on  "" the complete infidel's guide to iran ! "" "" """,implicit_hate,Iranians,Iranians consider Jews infidels,irony,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'jmt': 'ORG'}, {'robert spencer': 'PER'}, {""infidel ' s guide"": 'MISC'}, {'iran': 'LOC'}]"
639861084887851008," rt black supremacist arrested for threatening to  "" kill all white people in the town "" "" | more : """,not_hate,,,,,[{'rt': 'ORG'}]
934621046224949248," rt crooked hillary you didn't lose because you couldn't portray yourself as an  "" agent of change "" "" you loss because you are a socialist agent of destruction . shut up hillary and stop whining ! """,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'hillary': 'PER'}, {'hillary': 'PER'}]"
370476364052168705," rt estonian pm :  "" i don't want blacks in estonia ; this is a white country "" "" via < well said . """,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'estonian': 'MISC'}, {'estonia': 'LOC'}]"
938169995401494528," we capitalize neither  "" white "" "" nor "" "" black . "" "" from our writer's guide : "" "" when referring to race  black and white are never capitalized . "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,[]
901459720954941440," when you said  "" we "" "" are you talking about the white supremacist  the nazis  the racist   the hate for o """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'##pre': 'MISC'}, {'nazis': 'MISC'}]"
659069742314102784,#istandwithsweden #isalutewhitepeople #thanksjews #whitegenocide,not_hate,,,,,"[{'istandsweden': 'ORG'}, {'isaluw': 'ORG'}, {'thanks': 'ORG'}, {'whitegenocide': 'ORG'}]"
624235111391690753,#whitelivesmatter #wakeupamerica #workingclass #whitepower,not_hate,,,,,"[{'whitelivesmatter': 'ORG'}, {'wakeupamerica': 'ORG'}, {'workingclass': 'ORG'}, {'whitepower': 'ORG'}]"
700401349687713792,' holocaust ' debate / comments / news claude lanzmann : just finnished this one  a must for you all as it give ...,not_hate,,,,,"[{'holocaust': 'MISC'}, {'claude lanzmann': 'PER'}]"
444254051933618177,. fine for #hobbylobby to believe life begins before birth  if a store can believe . it can't be forced to have an abortion .,not_hate,,,,,[{'hobbylobby': 'ORG'}]
807439485000503296,. pretty sure trump doesn't want incompetents on his team ...,not_hate,,,,,[{'trump': 'PER'}]
905185677637242887,3 ) a white supremacist drove his car into a crowd of people,not_hate,,,,,[{'supre': 'MISC'}]
251422864232808449,: : hate posters ? you want hate buddy ? read the koran . goo ...,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are hateful people,white_grievance,,[{'koran': 'MISC'}]
939612494796132355,: cnn wants black people to think the president is racist . look around you  your,not_hate,,,,,[{'cnn': 'ORG'}]
548214253497249792,: hunt for white women : black racist serial killer confesses to 41 murders,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people are violent,stereotypical,,[]
538568467545604096,: if you're racist unfollow me . i hate you . you need to die .,not_hate,,,,,[]
184109665108504579,: looks like he was a fan of the islamic jew-hate reza aslan peddles as critique of i ...,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are hateful,stereotypical,,"[{'islamic jew': 'MISC'}, {'aslan peddles': 'PER'}]"
883558989098872838,: ridiculous ! he should defend human dignity planet climate changerecism / fascism / terror white racist wright,not_hate,,,,,[{'wright': 'PER'}]
924319698547720192,: white power !,not_hate,Minorities,Minorities are low-grade human beings,incitement,,[{'white': 'MISC'}]
610888901876711424,a must-read for churches and nonprofits from and #religiousfreedom,not_hate,,,,,[]
726114358661533696,actually it's the other way around . the french resistance would already have sent #trucons to the guillotine .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'french': 'MISC'}, {'trucons': 'PER'}]"
734069341264568320,agree with mary . amren seems confused by jewish achievement and iq .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'mary': 'PER'}, {'amren': 'PER'}, {'jewish': 'MISC'}]"
675330521048719364,ahmad javed appointed as the next ambassador of india to the kingdom of saudi arabia .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'ahmad javed': 'PER'}, {'india': 'LOC'}, {'saudi arabia': 'LOC'}]"
900856991010103297,and a white supremacist would be a crazy white dude . just saying .,not_hate,,,,,[{'supre': 'MISC'}]
490968338458509312,and are you a white european aryan  because most of these hitler fan boys hate anybody that isn't ? ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'european aryan': 'MISC'}, {'hitler': 'PER'}]"
888781661265055746,and dems  esp . city govts  are the ones who want poor people to think they can't make it off the dem plantation .,implicit_hate,Democrats,That democrats don't help poor people,,,"[{'dem': 'MISC'}, {'dem': 'ORG'}]"
899042367621214210,antifa is acting just like the kkk ... dressing in all black instead of white  hiding / mask identity  beating people of their race & etc,not_hate,,,,,"[{'antifa': 'ORG'}, {'kkk': 'ORG'}]"
929893092299300864,antiwhites hate white solidarity . their hate for white european self preservation knows no,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are hateful,white_grievance,,[{'european': 'MISC'}]
521162618367512576,are a bunch of religious bigots . i hope you experience something similar to what you put gay people through in your own lives.fuck u .,explicit_hate,,,,,[]
774362837057667073,are forever white racemass murderers ! ! !,implicit_hate,Whites,Whites are racist and violent.,white_grievance,,[]
724531599509884928,are you out of your mind people going with out food here homeless sleep on streets americans,not_hate,,,,,[{'americans': 'MISC'}]
425297747260882944,article 356 should be invoked and the aap govt should be dismissed : subramanian swamy  bjp leader ( times now ),not_hate,,,,,"[{'aap': 'ORG'}, {'subramanian swamy': 'PER'}, {'bjp': 'ORG'}, {'times now': 'ORG'}]"
938092479588560903,but america decided long ago to replace its white population with non-whites  & the more non-white immigration there is the faster this can precede . you're supposed to be celebrating diversity  i . e . your own racial & ethnic decline & ultimate demise . your country demands it !,not_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
720859443408150532,clinton to white people : ' we need to recognize our privilege ' via,not_hate,,,,,[{'clinton': 'PER'}]
938849829953986561,democratically  he won the presidency . end of issue . the dems have been trying to stop his agenda sin,not_hate,,,,,[{'dem': 'ORG'}]
944147802644459520,everything this president is being accused of by u libtards is exactly wha,not_hate,,,,,[{'u libt': 'ORG'}]
381257565986111488,freedom from religion group is such troublemakers  after texas cheerleaders too,not_hate,,,,,"[{'freedom from': 'ORG'}, {'texas': 'LOC'}]"
691178045437300736,german govt . forbade police to name north,not_hate,,,,,"[{'german': 'MISC'}, {'north': 'LOC'}]"
944473141102997504,germany : the most important thing is to educate refugees about the holocaust via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'germany': 'LOC'}, {'holocaust': 'MISC'}]"
490962990720499712,hamas is the only one who lies and all those like hamas . the only gobels are those who believe hamas .,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'hamas': 'ORG'}, {'hamas': 'PER'}, {'go': 'PER'}, {'hamas': 'PER'}]"
834858863174119424,how about conservatism is the political philosophy of dishonor and cowardice ? #cpac2017,not_hate,,,,,[{'cpac': 'ORG'}]
929022450515480576,i am not a white nationalist or a leftist in anyway but in your predicament  what gave you the idea to,not_hate,,,,,[]
925037778177482752,i guess whites and blacks dont belong in civilized countries according to your rhetoric .,not_hate,,,,,[]
705184110545768449,i have a sense carson was staying in just to split votes from cruz . he's been chummy with dt and giving me chris christie vibes,not_hate,,,,,"[{'carson': 'PER'}, {'cruz': 'PER'}, {'dt': 'PER'}, {'chris christie': 'PER'}]"
686273443176775681,i have warned of sharia finance for years,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are threatening,,,[{'sha': 'MISC'}]
896809946209234946,i think white people are waking up in unprecedented numbers,implicit_hate,White people,White people are beginning to realize what's happening to them,white_grievance,,[]
634149337103212550,i'd like to hear more from #joshduggar and the family research council about the sanctity of marriage . #bwahaha !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'joshduggar': 'PER'}, {'family research council': 'ORG'}]"
901512389086019589,i'm amazed people were actually able to coordinate grassroots coups and rebellions back in the day when,not_hate,,,,,[]
847795052093079553,i'm not a racist at all but i mean all the numbers are saying caucaisian people are set to disappear soon so i'm for keeping the race,implicit_hate,White people,White people are being driven extinct,incitement,,[{'caucaisian': 'MISC'}]
945493374433419265,identity europe is a race baiting organization which when confronted with any opposition  become cowards . the ultimate snowflakes . after using terror tactics against immigrants and black people  you get pushback and hide behind skin color . failures .,not_hate,,,,,[{'identity europe': 'ORG'}]
853283273996255232,it's no secret that white people are native to areas like that . do u now consider orient white ?,not_hate,,,,,[{'orient': 'LOC'}]
835184034854547458,its a planned growth of africans & a planned elimination of whites  #whitegenocide  #kalergi  #maga #tcot #trump #altright #sjw #buildawall,implicit_hate,Blacks,Blacks are trying to destroy whites.,white_grievance,,"[{'africans': 'MISC'}, {'whites': 'MISC'}, {'whitegenocide': 'ORG'}, {'kalergi': 'ORG'}, {'maga': 'ORG'}, {'tc': 'ORG'}, {'trump': 'ORG'}, {'altright': 'ORG'}, {'sw': 'ORG'}, {'buildawall': 'ORG'}]"
932309379172495365,its ok to be white - the book,implicit_hate,,,white_grievance,,[]
468722320614248448,japanese pm abe shinzo follows a total of 3 people on twitter . narendra modi is one of them . via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'japanese': 'MISC'}, {'abe shinzo': 'PER'}, {'narendra modi': 'PER'}, {'via': 'ORG'}]"
423138149968011266,kumar bishwas may join bjp soon after being targeted by islamic fundamentalists,not_hate,,,,,"[{'kumar bishwas': 'PER'}, {'bjp': 'ORG'}, {'islamic': 'MISC'}]"
392327342493671424,moscow authorities ban nationalist rally after racial riots | read more : via,not_hate,,,,,[{'moscow': 'LOC'}]
907488230836199425,no  she could have run and tripped over people - she could have had a fr,not_hate,,,,,[]
840084658666713089,no woman has the right to kill an unborn baby ! it's not her body  it's the baby's body  she's choosing to kill . open your eyes ! ! !,not_hate,,,,,[]
382827832407109632,now it is full of jew and government infiltrators .,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews look to take power.,stereotypical,,[{'jew': 'MISC'}]
855206872126717952,one of the questions never asked : if africans had won any of their repeated wars for european conquest  would we still be slaves ? of course .,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'africans': 'MISC'}, {'european': 'MISC'}]"
892751690620780544,only racist if you're white  this just makes you smart .,implicit_hate,White people,White people are racist/the only race capable of being racist,white_grievance,,[]
840324729093283840,prof kmac is right all along that jews have been manipulate white-euro people,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are conspiring against whites,stereotypical,,"[{'kmac': 'PER'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}, {'white': 'MISC'}, {'euro': 'MISC'}]"
918503605975617539,racist ppl it's what y'all are ! you have your own criminals here in the dsa is not more usa that's why you are divided states of america,not_hate,,,,,"[{'dsa': 'ORG'}, {'usa': 'LOC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
931574910798966785,so in order to slice the initial problem of white supremacy .. you attack black people who value the love in our communities and are willing to now stand up . circumstances your people put on us systematically .. yet i never know any white people who have been through this for yrs,not_hate,,,,,[]
913669399868973056,stop talking to the fbi hunter,not_hate,,,,,[{'fbi': 'ORG'}]
653272681895211008,syrian war would redefine future of global #economy spanish media #russiavsisil #syria,not_hate,,,,,"[{'syrian': 'MISC'}, {'spanish': 'MISC'}, {'russia': 'LOC'}, {'##isil': 'ORG'}, {'syria': 'LOC'}]"
727639462386208768,the #trucons !,not_hate,,,,,[{'trucons': 'ORG'}]
917086979153592321,the biggest racist in uk politics - diane i hate whites abbott !,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'uk': 'LOC'}, {'diane': 'PER'}, {'abbott': 'PER'}]"
519191430762225665,the commercial and industrial proliferation of nuclear wastes  more than any other issue hangs as an ominous pall over our heads,not_hate,,,,,[]
461918629928255489,the uncultured and uncivilized men from cental india who invaded asia destroyed the great persian culture  destroyed remains of indus,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'cent': 'LOC'}, {'india': 'LOC'}, {'asia': 'LOC'}, {'persian': 'MISC'}, {'indus': 'LOC'}]"
942807242285383685,they hate white people with a passion .,not_hate,,,,,[]
424860910713192449,they say they are anti-racist  but what they really are is anti-white ! via,implicit_hate,Minorities,Minorities are anti white.,white_grievance,,[]
829440607873617921,this country has a serious problem with corporate politics . big mac nation . diabetes and single mothers = end result,not_hate,,,,,[{'big mac': 'ORG'}]
926222203334680577,this is bs . i agree on all getting along . i didn't think the optics was so important as long,not_hate,,,,,[]
713784408176783360,today is national horse protection day ! please sign and share our petition -->,not_hate,,,,,[]
736792356544995328,trucons lament the rise of white identity politics via #altright #trucons #neocons,not_hate,,,,,"[{'trucons': 'ORG'}, {'altright': 'ORG'}, {'trucons': 'ORG'}, {'neocon': 'ORG'}]"
842142881263497216,true . swpl types weapjize blacks vs bad whites  and fetishize them w / mandingo or queen ( ie beyonc ) fantasies,implicit_hate,Whites,Whites are weak and feeble.,,,"[{'swpl': 'ORG'}, {'mano': 'MISC'}, {'ie beyon': 'PER'}]"
663248377791016960,we all support you guys keep up the good work,not_hate,,,,,[]
900953998210891778,what did you expect  back than demos and repubs were white racist runing these country . demos were beganing to yield to minorty demannds .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'demos': 'ORG'}, {'rep': 'ORG'}, {'demos': 'ORG'}]"
876643278803927040,when the saxon began to hate : white man smashes van into moslem crowd in london  at least 10 report via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'saxon': 'MISC'}, {'moslem': 'MISC'}, {'london': 'LOC'}]"
886819831592480768,whites don't contribute anything other than labor and kids .,implicit_hate,white people,white people are uneducated,,,[{'whites': 'MISC'}]
653200794804555776,who's hosting khurshid kasuri : 1 ) advisor-speech writer-friend of advani ji . 2 ) rajya sabha tv.whom to blame ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'khurshid kasuri': 'PER'}, {'advani ji': 'PER'}, {'rajya sabha tv': 'ORG'}]"
897625894499622912,yesterday was white supremacists  today is white nationalists  tomorrow just saying white you'll come as racist . control the perception .,not_hate,,,,,[]
59743762250874880,you're right  and of all the groups in america that are being trampled upon  the white working class is getting it the worst,not_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
718990165335642112,your ugly white cis male scum . your what's wrong with america .,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'cis': 'MISC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
930890495722774528,youre a racist moron .,not_hate,,,,,[]
537630568553644032,"  "" : latest unhinged anti-white rant at #ferguson "" "" ugly black lesbian . #negrogeddon """,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people are anti-white,stereotypical,,"[{'ferguson': 'PER'}, {'negrogeddon': 'MISC'}]"
564392777371631616,"  "" : muslims threaten female army cadets with beheading "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,[{'muslims': 'MISC'}]
254700110808752130,"  "" : new zealand : white faces will soon be a minority via "" "" """,implicit_hate,white people,White people are becoming the minority.,incitement,,[{'new zealand': 'LOC'}]
925202155589505024,"  "" : we need a worldview  not a universal outlook #tcot #nrx #altright "" "" fyi """,not_hate,,,,,[]
283294699899461632,"  "" : we wish you all a white christmas and a brighter new year : via "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,[]
931958777322057729,"  "" an individual white person being portrayed as desirable  talented  or fashionable can be tolerated  but only if that person signals against the collective interests of his or her people . "" "" said gregory hood  a blatant racist ! ! ! """,not_hate,,,,,[{'gregory hood': 'PER'}]
266953794225577984,"  "" by the quran  we will kill you all  you faggots ! "" "" : muslims attack gay club in paris  beating patrons and sprayi ... """,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'quran': 'MISC'}, {'muslims': 'MISC'}, {'paris': 'LOC'}]"
558018716055904257,"  "" caring for vulnerable includes caring for unborn children & their mothers "" "" says in response to #sotu call to value all life """,not_hate,,,,,[{'sotu': 'ORG'}]
278639492468989952,"  "" defense of marriage act doesn't violate equal protection . "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'defense of marriage act': 'MISC'}, {'equal protection': 'MISC'}]"
524332677369827329,"  "" everything not forbidden is compulsory . "" "" - t . h . white """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'t': 'PER'}, {'. h. white': 'PER'}]"
244938732065660928,"  "" i lost my faith in atheism . now i love god with all my heart . "" "" - kirk cameron """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'god': 'PER'}, {'kirk cameron': 'PER'}]"
889917651828568067,"  "" impressions over sessions "" "" - alt lite """,not_hate,,,,,[{'alt lite': 'ORG'}]
796508184265433089,"  "" it has finally hit them like a 2x4 between the eyes that white america is not the dying corpse they assumed it to be . "" "" - rocky suhayda """,not_hate,non-white people,non-white people are oppressors,white_grievance,,"[{'america': 'LOC'}, {'rocky suhayda': 'PER'}]"
908787595127218176,"  "" it is shocking that such a high percentage of people even believe that america has a ' white  european heritage . ' "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'america': 'LOC'}, {'european': 'MISC'}]"
937051454027771904,"  "" optics frat "" "" - i . e .  "" "" i'm interested in being a spectacle for the anti-white media  not organizing white people into a cohesive pro-white movement . "" "" being a clown will get your media coverage . is your goal is to get on tv for a 2 minute hate ? """,implicit_hate,Journalists,Journalist hate whites,incitement,,[{'frat': 'MISC'}]
269818814965899264,"  "" parents who contacted alliance defending freedom relieved that forced abortion is off the table for their daughter "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,[{'alliance defending freedom': 'ORG'}]
817116575736152064,"  "" people "" "" is being generous """,not_hate,,,,,[]
801242697440919552,"  "" reddit's pro-white community "" ""  so  reddit then ? """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'reddit': 'ORG'}, {'reddit': 'ORG'}]"
941001616785846273,"  "" the failures of the southern-dixie patriots in virginia and alabama are due to soros and mccain  for the misfortune of the people ' russian colomnists ' tzargrad tv ' """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'southern': 'MISC'}, {'dixie': 'ORG'}, {'virginia': 'LOC'}, {'alabama': 'LOC'}, {'soros': 'PER'}, {'mccain': 'PER'}, {'russian': 'MISC'}, {'col': 'ORG'}, {'tzargrad tv': 'ORG'}]"
756330709384437761,"  "" we must break free from the petty politics of the past . "" "" #rncincle """,not_hate,,,,,[]
807666445505138688,"  "" we must have an all-white america ... in which our children and our grandchildren will play and go to school with other white children . "" "" - glr """,implicit_hate,whites,Whites are better than other races,incitement,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
589152067127746560,"  "" what our bros & sis experiencing in me : what is coming for us in west . must rise up and awaken . "" "" #bgun """,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are invaders,incitement,,"[{'bros': 'ORG'}, {'sis': 'ORG'}, {'west': 'LOC'}]"
843831195897073664,"  "" why wont these people vote for the party that obviously hates them ? ? ? "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,[]
845580440576688128," 15 part series  "" islam & isis "" "" can be found here """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'islam': 'MISC'}, {'isis': 'MISC'}]"
662337122595016704," >  "" @ sardaanarohit "" "" < is fake profile by aap """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'sardaanarohit': 'ORG'}, {'aap': 'ORG'}]"
694985005915901952," a  "" true conservative "" "" wants to know how we will secure the border of ukraine and south korea """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'ukraine': 'LOC'}, {'south korea': 'LOC'}]"
868216734028894212," a ( ( (  "" white male "" "" ) ) ) """,not_hate,,,,,[]
522347879612944388," adl demands internet censorship again / now it's  "" cyber hate "" "" : the title of this piece should be ' supremacist j ... """,not_hate,,,,,[{'adl': 'ORG'}]
599638600238682112," african  "" refugee "" "" was only here nine days before raping a woman | full story : """,implicit_hate,Immigrants,Immigrants are rapists,stereotypical,,[{'african': 'MISC'}]
625309687152549888," and of course   "" anti-racist "" "" is a code word for "" "" anti-white "" "" . "" "" self-hating jews "" "" are nothing compared with self-hating white people . """,implicit_hate,white people,all white identifying people are racist,white_grievance,,[{'jews': 'MISC'}]
836255634593038338," by  "" independent media  "" "" w . means the legacy mainstream media which is upset its customary privileges have been revoked : """,not_hate,,,,,[]
618594196673314817," cincinnati police : officer who dubbed the 40 blacks attacking 1 white person a  "" hate crime "" "" was wrong ... : """,not_hate,,,,,[{'cincinnati': 'LOC'}]
643569745145528320," cuckservatives : gop now officially the party of  "" white paranoia "" "" via """,not_hate,,,,,[{'gop': 'ORG'}]
829744970709999618," do most conservtism  inc people experience  "" cuck panic "" "" when featured by media matters ? """,not_hate,,,,,[{'conservtism inc': 'ORG'}]
524794881525698560," goad  you are the living proof that  "" white supremacy "" "" is bunk . """,not_hate,,,,,[]
906584381065658369," hayek was also a very milquetoast libertarian . road to serfdom :  "" central planning = totalitarian  but """,not_hate,,,,,[{'hayek': 'PER'}]
434015254394466304," he's likely right rt : iranian ayatollah : americans  "" don't have the guts "" "" to attack iran """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'iranian': 'MISC'}, {'##yat': 'PER'}, {'##ollah': 'MISC'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}, {'iran': 'LOC'}]"
845748487371325441," i feel like it is all just  "" white supremacy "" "" lol """,not_hate,,,,,[{'white supremacy': 'MISC'}]
770460776993783809," i like jared taylor .  "" he white "" "" """,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are undesirable,incitement,,"[{'jared taylor': 'PER'}, {'he': 'PER'}]"
834887963611922434," kkk = kreosote kornhole kids . give in charity or stop getting hungry .  "" give in charity . "" "" - jesus """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'k': 'ORG'}, {'kreosote kornhole': 'ORG'}, {'jesus': 'PER'}]"
816444879156822016," milo is a  "" white nationalist "" "" according to . i'm sure actual white nationalists like would be surprised to hear that . """,not_hate,,,,,[{'milo': 'PER'}]
933389045811634177," no  he's a racist . when black people complain or disrespect him  he always has an overreaction . way out of proportion . he expects his white  "" specialness "" "" to be above reproach . """,not_hate,,,,,[]
937769172796362752," no doubt that anonymous internet forums attract cringeworthy low sexual value males who like to lash out at women . lots of  "" edgy politics "" "" - even irl - attract a similar crowd . still  can't beat the internet for pro-white memes like "" "" anti-racist is a code word for anti-white . "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'irl': 'ORG'}, {'racist': 'MISC'}]"
897094962042609664," oh  yes ... all those neo-nazis / white nationalist are all about  "" learnin ' "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'neo': 'MISC'}, {'nazis': 'MISC'}, {'white nationalist': 'MISC'}]"
805493894356013057," oh noes ! tariffs - what a  "" chilling "" "" word ! it completely goes against what "" "" true conservatism "" "" is all about ! """,not_hate,,,,,[]
844383860410454016," race cucks like paul ryan should be banished to live in a  "" diverse "" "" neighbrhd if they want t spout such nonsense """,implicit_hate,Progressives,Progressives push their views on others,irony,,"[{'paul ryan': 'PER'}, {'ne': 'LOC'}]"
917599072470687744," right ? what good is  "" white supremacy "" "" if it leads to a white minority . """,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people want to displace white people,other,,[]
563772521015570432," rt  "" #jihadiaap "" "" is now trending at rank 4 in india """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'jihad': 'MISC'}, {'##iaap': 'ORG'}, {'india': 'LOC'}]"
547831185238265856," rt  "" : does the kkk .. hate black animals / pets ? .. since they not white ? "" "" ? """,not_hate,,,,,[{'kkk': 'ORG'}]
286995761617575936," rt  "" : proud white women speak out against white genocide ( video ) via "" "" """,implicit_hate,Minorities,Minorities are trying to wipe out whites,white_grievance,,[{'rt': 'ORG'}]
557824311403495425," rt  "" : start measures like cancelling licences of swiss banks in india if they quickly don't return our money . "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'swiss': 'MISC'}, {'india': 'LOC'}]"
843995205833543680," rt  "" and  at the same time  in restoring a captive people to their long-lost father-land  with bright prospects for the future "" "" lincoln on clay """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'lincoln': 'LOC'}, {'on': 'MISC'}, {'clay': 'MISC'}]"
404019616466206720," rt  "" i hate you all "" "" - racist note from the black boy who raped his white teacher & slit her throat via #wr """,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people are violent rapists,stereotypical,,"[{'i': 'MISC'}, {'you all': 'MISC'}]"
879353657376075776," rt  "" this win for #trinitylutheran church is a win for the freedoms that americans have long exercised . "" "" #religiousfreedom """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'trinitylutheran church': 'ORG'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}]"
834809906523938818," rt #cpac2017 : alt-right denounced w / speech journos said  "" makes no sense . "" "" attendees  press flock to . the momentum is ours . """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'cp': 'ORG'}, {'alt - right': 'ORG'}, {'journos': 'PER'}]"
648875135106199553," rt .  "" there are no #plannedparenthood clinics that have mammogram machines "" "" . #defundpp """,not_hate,,,,,[]
381557840759910400," rt :  "" robert spencer must be shot head "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,[{'robert spencer': 'PER'}]
210857835964276737," rt : how #jews feel about #whitepeople -  "" the white race is the cancer of human history . "" "" - jewess susan sontag #hate #israel # r ... """,implicit_hate,jews,jews hate white people,stereotypical,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}, {'jew': 'MISC'}, {'susan sontag': 'PER'}, {'israel': 'LOC'}]"
930715058417446912," rt : so ayaan ok but not me ? oops  dan :  "" "" no one has upset the islamophobia cabal more than robert spencer . first  he knows m """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'ayaan': 'PER'}, {'o': 'PER'}, {'dan': 'PER'}, {'islam': 'MISC'}, {'##op': 'ORG'}, {'##ho': 'MISC'}, {'##bia cabal': 'ORG'}, {'robert spencer': 'PER'}]"
184348431093997568," rt : white racialists rally in edmonton  alberta and london  ontario as a commemoration of  "" white pride worldwide day "" "" ... """,implicit_hate,Minorities,Minorities are inferior to whites,incitement,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'edmonton': 'LOC'}, {'alberta': 'LOC'}, {'london ontario': 'LOC'}, {'white pride worldwide day': 'MISC'}]"
811671182831337472," rt another hate hoax : police nab notorious  "" white supremacist "" "" who drew swastikas around a college """,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are conspiring,white_grievance,,[{'rt': 'ORG'}]
486237476768731137," rt australia returns non-white invaders ; jewish  "" human rights "" "" groups flip out | more : """,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are invaders,white_grievance,,"[{'rt australia': 'ORG'}, {'jewish': 'MISC'}]"
608733922030186496," rt black people can't be racist  "" : ohio man pushes white jogger into traffic because he "" "" hates whites "" "" via """,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people hates white people,incitement,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'ohio': 'LOC'}]"
850854244420796416," rt dawa = > barbaric  totalitarian political ideology intent on enslaving all human beings for  "" allah "" "" imagine founding a club on these principles """,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are barbaric.,stereotypical,,"[{'dawa': 'MISC'}, {'allah': 'MISC'}]"
828481463381172225," rt jesus's teaching on judgement :  "" let he who is without sin cast the first stone "" "" . are you  senator ? are you ? """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'jesus': 'PER'}]"
522409919128301568," rt ky christian printer blaine adamson targeted by  "" human rights commission "" "" #religiousfreedom """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt ky': 'ORG'}, {'blaine adamson': 'PER'}, {'human rights commission': 'ORG'}]"
675386139377709056," rt rt #makeamericagreatagain #trump2016  "" thank you for all of your support  south carolina ! "" "" ; """,implicit_hate,Republicans,Republicans are hateful to minorities and liberals,,,"[{'rt rt': 'ORG'}, {'makeamerica': 'ORG'}, {'trump': 'MISC'}, {'south carolina': 'LOC'}]"
355070439497801729," rt rt : #doma  doesn't  "" end the national debate over marriage . "" "" #1m1w """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rt rt': 'ORG'}, {'dom': 'PER'}]"
945132880056827904," rt since when was jesus  "" mixed race "" "" ? ... please stop trying to stick jesus and christianity into your criminal communist ideology . don't tell me you're like those bbc anti-white racists that depict julius caesar and achilles as black men in the name of "" "" diversity "" "" and inclusiveness """,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are criminals,white_grievance,,"[{'rt': 'ORG'}, {'jesus': 'PER'}, {'jesus': 'MISC'}, {'christianity': 'MISC'}, {'bbc': 'ORG'}, {'julius caesar': 'PER'}, {'achilles': 'PER'}]"
420285099108597760," rt why doesnt tell ..  "" aap kuch lete kyun nahin "" "" .. #coughcough .. """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'kyun nahin': 'MISC'}, {'cough': 'PER'}, {'##co': 'MISC'}]"
694929265821876224," ted cruz and paul ryan called the trans pacific partnership  "" a fair deal for the american worker "" "" """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'ted cruz': 'PER'}, {'paul ryan': 'PER'}, {'trans pacific': 'ORG'}, {'american': 'MISC'}]"
924278672701444097," they smother the good white people of america ! they need to be hung  brother  "" south "" "" ! """,implicit_hate,immigrants,Immigrants hurt the white people.,threatening,,"[{'america': 'LOC'}, {'south': 'LOC'}]"
890595912241860609," this is lame  where's the creativity ? and why put your white boy in the staffs (  "" house n word "" "" position ? you can do better . """,explicit_hate,,,,,[]
857373032188436481," thrilling . many  "" whites "" "" are against you . so . not a united "" "" bloc "" "" . """,not_hate,,,,,[]
824639897277313025," typical leftist chant   "" racist !  racist ! it rings hollow when it's every other word "" "" you people "" "" use . """,not_hate,,,,,[]
807328396833419269," uk sport displays anti white racism when they cut funding for  "" white sports "" "" prior to tokyo olympics ! """,implicit_hate,white people,White people are racist.,white_grievance,,"[{'uk': 'LOC'}, {'tokyo': 'LOC'}, {'olympics': 'MISC'}]"
371269803056459778," us should have leaders this brave rt :  "" i don't want blacks in estonia ; this is a white country "" "" via """,implicit_hate,Black,Black people shouldn't live in Estonia,incitement,,"[{'us': 'MISC'}, {'rt': 'ORG'}, {'estonia': 'LOC'}, {'via': 'ORG'}]"
854039751288029185," w / bad intentions . & don't  "" but the other people ... "" "" i'm well aware of antifa & so are pd . i'm talking to you all right now """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'anti': 'ORG'}, {'pd': 'ORG'}]"
897888036939235328," well  i do believe it's time for spencer to step aside . along with the retards that started the  "" white sharia now "" "" chants . """,implicit_hate,conservative whites,conservative whites are anti-women,,,"[{'spencer': 'PER'}, {'white sharia now': 'MISC'}]"
661386606960447488," what part of  "" expect us "" "" did you not comprehend ? buncha ignorant podunks ! #opkkk """,not_hate,,,,,"[{'expect us': 'MISC'}, {'podunk': 'MISC'}]"
875611656117551106," when you google  "" cuck knight "" "" ... """,implicit_hate,Conservative men,Conservative men are weak and effeminate,,,[{'cuck knight': 'MISC'}]
822064572559290369," white people have threatened the safety of  "" americans "" "" since the beginning  before this was even america """,implicit_hate,White people,White people are violent and have a history of killing people,,,"[{'americans': 'MISC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
781542330897760256," you think a century of iq science is  "" group think talking points "" "" ? that's moronic . """,not_hate,,,,,[]
822295169659764738,! ! ! #racists with a racist-group for a racist-cause ... there's ' nothing ' fair about deceptive ! ! ! / / /,not_hate,,,,,[]
768854642063249409,#altrightmeans becoming great again .,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are inferior,incitement,,[{'altrightmeans': 'ORG'}]
768830400407932929,#altrightmeans that deus vult !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'altright': 'ORG'}, {'de': 'MISC'}]"
675724941044621312,#antiwhite #14words #whitelivesmatter #frankfurtschool #culturalmarxism,not_hate,,,,,"[{'antiwhite': 'ORG'}, {'whitelivesmatter': 'ORG'}, {'frankfurtschool': 'ORG'}, {'cultural': 'ORG'}]"
801486977430388742,#aryan men & women will either rise up to fight for their heritage  children  & future  or the white race will cease to exist . choose now .,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people want to displace white people,incitement,,[{'aryan': 'MISC'}]
783765215863250945,#blacklivesmatter and again . black on white crime ! what a surprise ...,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people kill white people,white_grievance,,[{'blacklivesmatter': 'ORG'}]
744928615637225473,#crookedhillary responsible for deaths of 200k + people in iraq afghanistan lybia & syria . #hillaryisjihad #trump2016 #trumptrain,not_hate,,,,,"[{'crookedhill': 'ORG'}, {'iraq': 'LOC'}, {'afghanistanbia': 'LOC'}, {'syria': 'LOC'}, {'hillary': 'ORG'}, {'trump': 'MISC'}, {'trumptrain': 'ORG'}]"
917405962130116609,#defundnfl stop paying to make people who hate you  your nation  your people rich . #wakeupwhiteman,implicit_hate,white people,White people depend on minorities.,incitement,,"[{'defundnfl': 'ORG'}, {'wakeupwhiteman': 'ORG'}]"
720674448018280448,#germany : non-white in one generation #auspol | read more : via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'germany': 'LOC'}, {'auspol': 'ORG'}]"
724771748680359936,#ghostsquad #opkkk #lulz bad children no website 4 u #anonresistance #classwar not #racewar,not_hate,,,,,"[{'ghosts': 'ORG'}, {'lu': 'ORG'}, {'an': 'ORG'}]"
902532542078652417,#iffootballdidntexist white men would fulfill their tribal instinct by standing up for their own kind  not worshipping negros who hate them .,implicit_hate,White people,White people support only white people,incitement,,[{'negro': 'MISC'}]
687274157382471680,#kansas takes a stand for human dignity  defunds #plannedparenthood #defundpp,implicit_hate,Liberals,Liberals want to murder babies through abortion,,,[{'kansas': 'LOC'}]
740366135279931392,#kkk  i do not mind your booklet . how can i support ? ? ?,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are enemies,incitement,,[{'kkk': 'ORG'}]
673250243320918017,#news channels must not invite mulla rats on tv to air anti-hindu views  they glorify invaders and anti-nationals on our money,explicit_hate,,,,,[{'hindu': 'MISC'}]
711787470824849408,#niggasfavoriteline them white people enslaved me 100 years ago  let's kill there great great great grand children,explicit_hate,,,,,[]
656611834204680192,#part28 : #stormtroopers ? #huh-they look more like a #21stcentury version of the #kkk #myfellowamericans,not_hate,,,,,"[{'kkk': 'MISC'}, {'my': 'MISC'}, {'##fell': 'ORG'}, {'##owamericans': 'MISC'}]"
860138744254541825,#problemsolved anti first amendment or antifa as they call themselves are terrorists and deserve their fate,not_hate,,,,,"[{'first amendment': 'MISC'}, {'anti': 'ORG'}]"
694344195276967936,#resistance #14words,not_hate,,,,,[]
729076625762062337,#ukraine #ukrainian thanks brothers . white pride worldwide . #wpww #14words .,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are not valuable,incitement,,"[{'ukraine': 'LOC'}, {'ukrainian': 'MISC'}, {'white pride': 'ORG'}, {'wpww': 'ORG'}]"
688775028133908480,#youtube the endgame - full white genocide documentary,not_hate,,,,,"[{'youtube': 'LOC'}, {'endgame': 'MISC'}]"
699766357341007873,' holocaust ' debate / comments / news how do you tell the difference between poles & ukrainians ? : when crema ...,not_hate,,,,,"[{'holocaust': 'MISC'}, {'poles': 'MISC'}, {'ukrainian': 'MISC'}]"
706547132249944064,' holocaust ' debate / comments / news kitty hart-moxon full testimony : ~ today i watched kitty hart full testi ...,not_hate,,,,,"[{'holocaust': 'MISC'}, {'kitty hart': 'PER'}, {'moxon': 'PER'}, {'kitty hart': 'PER'}]"
935619193084444672,( ( ( white nationalist ) ) ),not_hate,,,,,[]
662381105467666432,( kkk ),not_hate,,,,,[{'kkk': 'ORG'}]
865239800852480000,( this is what an iq test tests  boys and girls . ),not_hate,,,,,[]
900583523563618305,* sigh * i hope you're trolling because he obviously means the ideals and values msm and democrats promote . its ok to hate evil,not_hate,,,,,"[{'ms': 'ORG'}, {'democrats': 'MISC'}]"
669280579083501576,* threatened .. no jmac .. he black too but don't arrest him,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people get arrested for no reason,,,[{'jmac': 'ORG'}]
886504069489082368,- : this is also the word ! #workingclass #cnnblackmail #fnn,not_hate,,,,,[]
793764675175391232,. #alert ; #splc has posted hitlists online that targets patriotic / christianamericans ; resulted in chick-fil-a shooting at . #maga,not_hate,,,,,"[{'splc': 'ORG'}, {'christianamerical': 'MISC'}]"
521308202172813312,. #wotd from islamism : the religion or culture of islam . buzz,not_hate,,,,,"[{'islam': 'MISC'}, {'islam': 'MISC'}]"
936251979017412608,. : trump wh separates itself from obama  highlights nativity scene via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'trump': 'PER'}, {'obama': 'PER'}]"
644613102504296448,. can you do the same to a baby born alive in a delivery room ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
799042224700825601,. hey watch this . #leftism = enabling #islamists since times before #crusades . #historyrepeats,implicit_hate,Democrates,Democrats want Muslims to defeat Christians,white_grievance,,"[{'left': 'MISC'}, {'islamist': 'MISC'}, {'history': 'ORG'}]"
626565474990575617,. is an amazing #plannedparenthood alternative that actually cares about women .,not_hate,,,,,[]
646686959629299712,. op ed : islamic doctrine of shariah is anti-constitutional . your future potus should agree .,implicit_hate,Islamic people,Islamic people are unconstitutional.,other,,[{'islamicria': 'MISC'}]
208930800035573760,. so much concern about christian people ! as a jew what is christ to you ?,not_hate,Jews,Jews don't like Christians.,,,"[{'christian': 'MISC'}, {'jew': 'MISC'}, {'christ': 'PER'}]"
853366941427400707,. video of of punching commies at berkeley free speech rally . right wing safety squads #berkeleyprotest,not_hate,,,,,"[{'berkeley': 'LOC'}, {'berkeley': 'ORG'}]"
818907260466368513,... contrast white pols saying sessions is racist and black pastors saying he's not !,not_hate,,,,,[]
835411608281075712,1 vote for braveheart . 2 votes for a gibson directed remake starring bale ( as bateman ) as wallace . in la .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'braveheart': 'PER'}, {'gibson': 'PER'}, {'bale': 'PER'}, {'bateman': 'PER'}, {'wallace': 'PER'}, {'la': 'LOC'}]"
708585797499428864,17yrs old . happy international women's day .,not_hate,,,,,"[{""international women ' s day"": 'MISC'}]"
904362587147653121,2 . we're not trying to persuade people in michigan  pennsylvania or in california . we're in the south  no more  no less .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'michigan': 'LOC'}, {'pennsylvania': 'LOC'}, {'california': 'LOC'}, {'south': 'LOC'}]"
839958346195226624,2 hollywood jews want us to feel bad for not importing jihadists whose doctrine has more jew hate than mein kampf,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'hollywood': 'LOC'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}, {'jihad': 'MISC'}, {'jew': 'MISC'}, {'mein kampf': 'MISC'}]"
833161526341140480,3 / ... people like me !,not_hate,,,,,[]
797029497706921984,58 % of white voter vote for trump = racist 95 % of black voters vote for obama = not racist,not_hate,,,,,"[{'trump': 'PER'}, {'obama': 'PER'}]"
855215956645355520,88 % of rapes are not interracial . so white men are systemically targeting white females .,not_hate,,,,,[]
846439671357935621,9 / anyway  there were always regional cultural divides  but the arrival of jews en masse in nyc was a great catalyst,not_hate,,,,,"[{'jews': 'MISC'}, {'nyc': 'LOC'}]"
215463839288922113,: . rips #doj for ' engaging in collusion ' with #jihad ...,not_hate,,,,,"[{'do': 'ORG'}, {'jihad': 'ORG'}]"
925656364780806144,: all because one man has the audacity to think it's ok to be white  and ok to not hate you,not_hate,,,,,[]
752993390178865152,: and of course #whenthugscry,not_hate,,,,,[{'when': 'ORG'}]
898220948121280512,: and throw in weekly standard these filthy white trash disgust me,implicit_hate,white people,white people are trashy,inferiority,,[]
853418855062007810,: antifa is a joke . bring them to the south .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'anti': 'ORG'}, {'##fa': 'MISC'}]"
228116902554238976,: breaking : white pride america merges with the national socialist movement ! via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'white pride': 'ORG'}, {'america': 'LOC'}, {'national socialist movement': 'ORG'}]"
922586110605246464,: confiscation and invasion of our consulate in san francisco by fbi  is deep hostility towards russian people and,not_hate,,,,,"[{'san francisco': 'LOC'}, {'fbi': 'ORG'}, {'russian': 'MISC'}]"
658709610073722880,: csp poll ( 2015 ): 29 % of muslim-americans : violence against those who insult muhammad is acceptable,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are dangerous,stereotypical,,"[{'csp': 'ORG'}, {'muslim': 'MISC'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}, {'muhammad': 'PER'}]"
788994120014585856,: cuckservatives : the constitution will save us ! via,not_hate,,,,,[]
303931100856737793,: der fhrer  adolf hitler - rare moments in colour ( video ),not_hate,,,,,"[{'der': 'ORG'}, {'f': 'MISC'}, {'adolf hitler': 'PER'}]"
663073473682677760,: elin krantz : just another dead white liberal female raped to death by non-white invader,implicit_hate,Immigrants,Immigrants are rapists,stereotypical,,[{'elin krantz': 'PER'}]
485468968509906944,: europe's awakening : greek racial nationalists has made contact with bavarian national socialists !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'europe': 'LOC'}, {'greek': 'MISC'}, {'bavarian': 'MISC'}]"
804685295513903104,: georgetown university prof : islamophobia causes jihad terror  white supremacists greater threat than jihadis .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'georgetown university': 'ORG'}, {'islam': 'MISC'}, {'jihad': 'MISC'}]"
349860280584507392,: good morning ! please call your senators as soon as possible today ! tell them to vote #noamnesty (202) 224-3121,not_hate,,,,,[]
916785488345817089,: hollywood jew harvey weinstein busted for decades-long sexual abuse of white women via,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are devious,stereotypical,,"[{'hollywood': 'LOC'}, {'harvey weinstein': 'PER'}]"
782250790752845824,: islam is not a race ? obama white house wants to change that,not_hate,Blacks,Blacks perpetuate special privilege.,white_grievance,,"[{'islam': 'MISC'}, {'obama white house': 'LOC'}]"
900974330242314242,: islamic republic of iran terrorist # cleric  _and it's different  the path of our people is i,not_hate,,,,,[{'islamic republic of iran': 'LOC'}]
233604811260579841,: jewish harvard professor wants to abolish the white race ! read more : via,implicit_hate,Jewish people,Jews hate white people.,stereotypical,,"[{'jewish': 'MISC'}, {'harvard': 'ORG'}, {'via': 'ORG'}]"
339793332182077440,: kanye west releases his most anti-white rap song ever sucks hes the most racist man alive ..,implicit_hate,Blacks,Blacks are bigoted,white_grievance,,[{'kanye west': 'PER'}]
271305546244698114,: knockout king in uk : anti-white racist attacks now spreading to europe ! read more : via ...,not_hate,,,,,"[{'king': 'MISC'}, {'uk': 'LOC'}, {'europe': 'LOC'}, {'via': 'ORG'}]"
939099692767596544,: my new uk-oriented #counterjihad novel is free today on amazon at merry christmas !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'uk': 'MISC'}, {'amazon': 'ORG'}, {'christmas': 'MISC'}]"
864976666531045376,: nice to know that tsunami didn't dampen their energy to stay in the 7th century .,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims want to subject the world to SHaria Law,irony,,[]
943624345032806400,: preach it elder  preach it ! ! the democrats have overseen the mass enslavement of citizens with their tre,not_hate,,,,,[{'democrats': 'MISC'}]
209989471201001473,: re : the holocaust industry's work in progress ...,not_hate,,,,,[]
296013422624141312,: rudolf hess  the martyr for peace t-shirt from the white resister,not_hate,,,,,"[{'rudolf hess': 'PER'}, {'martyr for peace': 'MISC'}, {'white': 'MISC'}, {'resister': 'ORG'}]"
510359920336977920,: same old propaganda machine mt us will lunch airstrikes agnst muslims ( majority casualties,not_hate,,,,,[{'mt us': 'ORG'}]
355981597272588289,: so mr spencer ... muslims hate you and in all your clever rhetoric  best you can do is hate them back ! #spoil,not_hate,,,,,"[{'spencer': 'PER'}, {'muslims': 'MISC'}]"
181845824110731265,: successful amren conference ! read about it here : .,not_hate,,,,,[{'amren': 'MISC'}]
280551509010296832,: the myth of the 20h century : #history #wwii #philosophy,not_hate,,,,,"[{'history': 'MISC'}, {'wwii': 'MISC'}]"
588774633823961088,: uk : racist black man punches pregnant white girl in stomach as onlookers watch in horror sit & watch,not_hate,,,,,[{'uk': 'LOC'}]
6701886421860352,: uk : students in islamic schools taught sharia amputation methods and that jews are conspiring to take over ...,implicit_hate,muslims,Muslims are teaching their children violent ways and to hate Jewish people,stereotypical,,"[{'uk': 'LOC'}, {'islamic': 'MISC'}, {'sharia': 'MISC'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}]"
272053853212528640,: where is the media outrage ? white man was lynched and robbed by a racist black gang ! ( video ) via ...,implicit_hate,Blacks,Blacks are violent criminals,white_grievance,,[]
794275352101031936,: whores of babylon : lena dunham celebrates white genocide via #whitegenocide #waronwhites,implicit_hate,People of color,People of color want white people to die out,white_grievance,,"[{'whores of': 'MISC'}, {'babylon': 'ORG'}, {'lena dunham': 'PER'}, {'white': 'MISC'}, {'white': 'MISC'}, {'##genoc': 'ORG'}, {'warw': 'ORG'}]"
875678865733144576,a certain 1400 years old religious ideology has proven to be the biggest killing machine of innocent people in human history,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are killers,stereotypical,,[]
909907199962607616,a future for white children ! in the same fashon as hitler youth  who were given the great honor of dying for hitler ! seig heil ! amen !,implicit_hate,minorities,minorities are inferior,incitement,,"[{'hitler': 'ORG'}, {'hitler': 'PER'}]"
885514512270577666,a look back : #scotus unanimously ( 9-0 ) gives alliance defending freedom  our clients and religious americans victory,not_hate,,,,,"[{'scotus': 'ORG'}, {'alliance defending freedom': 'ORG'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}]"
918846912190586882,a make america white evangelical male event .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'make': 'MISC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}, {'white': 'MISC'}]"
936667473239097344,a metro of 10 million people and only shows up for #katesteinle,not_hate,,,,,[{'kate': 'PER'}]
203626059529326592,a really thorough explanation : clarifying the count of marriage amendments and referenda via,not_hate,,,,,[]
352924738231873536,a white man's response to frederick douglass on independence day - - #4thofjuly #july4th,implicit_hate,White people,White people are racists,,,"[{'frederick douglass': 'PER'}, {'independence day': 'MISC'}]"
436541969955696640,aap alleges rs 22000- cr scam in maharashtras power sector,not_hate,,,,,"[{'aap': 'ORG'}, {'maharashtra': 'LOC'}]"
915747850276999168,according to the southern poverty law center  they are a hate group that is against immigration ( except by white western europeans ) .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'southern poverty law center': 'ORG'}, {'western europeans': 'MISC'}]"
932596905695047680,accusations against pastors ? that doesn't sound credible . never would men of god take advantage of a young person .,not_hate,,,,,[{'god': 'ORG'}]
732264411994427392,action alert : oppose california taxpayer-funded health care for illegal aliens,not_hate,,,,,[{'california': 'LOC'}]
817595276714119169,actual white hispanic vs . not a white hispanic,not_hate,,,,,"[{'hispanic': 'MISC'}, {'hispanic': 'MISC'}]"
897595962553749506,add creating dependent society of poor to be under liberal government control & illegally spying on americans courtesy of bho,not_hate,,,,,"[{'americans': 'MISC'}, {'b': 'ORG'}]"
489340430589239296,afghanistan : muslim suicide bomber kills 89 muslims y'day = 1/2 no.of ppl killed by #israel in 10days ... any outrage ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'afghanistan': 'LOC'}, {'muslim': 'MISC'}, {'israel': 'LOC'}]"
871889551870087170,after taking over the countries they continued to kill christians  jews and other religions . ottoman empire continued to kill until ~ 1920,not_hate,,,,,[{'ottoman empire': 'LOC'}]
747596565909475328,al qaeda urges lone wolves to target whites  to avoid ' hate crime ' label | fox news |,not_hate,,,,,"[{'al qaeda': 'ORG'}, {'fox news': 'ORG'}]"
900203692263190528,algebra is an arabic word . a little hint as to its cultural origins .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'algebra': 'MISC'}, {'arabic': 'MISC'}]"
829716380786237441,all jews should be evicted from white countries,implicit_hate,jews,jews are inferior,threatening,,[{'jews': 'MISC'}]
901239757241561091,all lives matter we are not black and white we are men and woman as soon as black lives matter sees that true hate and racism will end,not_hate,,,,,[{'black': 'MISC'}]
911338462158172160,all the republicans are doing is pulling white america into the quicksand ! we must let go of them if we are to survive !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'republicans': 'MISC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
677968896150867968,all white are not aryans ; why are they trying to board the bandwagon of aryans ?,implicit_hate,non-aryans,non-aryans are not pure,other,,"[{'aryan': 'MISC'}, {'aryan': 'MISC'}]"
589122262755889152,allied soldiers raped almost one million german women  historian finds | read more :,not_hate,,,,,[{'german': 'MISC'}]
841116845390225408,america has always been about letting in people who hate you to call you racist for not letting in enough other people who also hate you .,not_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
746510545411407874,america was also 0 % white stretching back tens of thousands of years in the past . nice talking point .,not_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
842835677737902081,america was classically liberal when america was white .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'america': 'LOC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
892942985532502016,america was founded by white people .,not_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
666744663919845376,america's poorest white town : abandoned by coal  swallowed by drugs,not_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
323095142313627652,amerikwa is in terminal decline due to self-hating marxist kikes controlling mainstream media and brainwashing white people .,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'amerikwa': 'ORG'}, {'ki': 'MISC'}]"
854759853662797830,an anti-immigration group is attacking an anti-racism group bc ... ? oh  right  you're actually just a #racist group & ok w / white immigrants .,not_hate,,,,,[{'bc': 'LOC'}]
752316233261854721,an honest conversation about race | jared taylor ( ) & #whiteguilt #westerncivilization,not_hate,,,,,"[{'jared taylor': 'PER'}, {'whiteguilt': 'ORG'}, {'western': 'MISC'}]"
855221440282578945,and almost all of the rapes white men commit are attacks on white women .,not_hate,,,,,[]
822304411095437312,and dylan roof white american male killed other americans . shall we deport all white american males ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'dylan roof': 'PER'}, {'american': 'MISC'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}, {'american': 'MISC'}]"
855230348774559750,and if the victim is a white woman  the crime is overwhelmingly a white perp .,not_hate,,,,,[]
901166421463486464,and white brits were actually the 1st slaves in america . history ppl ! history !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'brit': 'MISC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
837548964429778944,angola used to be a prosperous portuguese colony . whites fled en masse in 1975,implicit_hate,White people,White people are racist and can't stand living in an area with people of color,incitement,,"[{'angola': 'LOC'}, {'portuguese': 'MISC'}]"
860489891267969025,another #trump & #prolife win ! house #ahca bill will defund planned parenthood : #foxnews #msnbc #cnn #nbc,not_hate,,,,,"[{'trump': 'PER'}, {'prolife': 'ORG'}, {'house': 'ORG'}, {'ah': 'ORG'}, {'planned parenthood': 'ORG'}, {'foxnews': 'ORG'}, {'msnbc': 'ORG'}, {'cnn': 'ORG'}, {'nbc': 'ORG'}]"
225883495967375361,another white fourteen year old gang-raped by africans in norway via #wpww,implicit_hate,africans,africans are rapists,stereotypical,,"[{'africans': 'MISC'}, {'norway': 'LOC'}, {'wpww': 'ORG'}]"
945681297632088064,anti white ? see i knew this was a scam . stop lying to yourself  snowflake . just because you criticizeracists and bigots  doesn't mean you're anti white . coward,implicit_hate,white folks,anti racist seen as anti white,,,[]
851288086596026368,anti white supremacist i like that,not_hate,,,,,[{'supremac': 'MISC'}]
939660639861137408,anti-degeneracy is actually underrated as a message for the alt right too,not_hate,,,,,[{'alt': 'MISC'}]
447092892814024704,anti-racist activist raped by non-white illegal immigrant after attending anti-racism festival via,not_hate,Illegals,Illegals rape whites,stereotypical,,[]
696933463413428224,anti-semitism is recurring problem in dutch schools via,not_hate,,,,,[{'dutch': 'MISC'}]
765237022596407297,anti-white tweets from hijab #rio2016 athlete . #deportallmuslims,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims should be deported.,threatening,,"[{'##ja': 'MISC'}, {'rio2016': 'MISC'}]"
883610947532804096,antifa are violent thugs and need to be physically removed . or do you still think they can be reasoned with in a logical manner ?,not_hate,,,,,[{'anti': 'ORG'}]
887803008972619777,any white guy not into identity politics is a fagg 0t,explicit_hate,,,,,[]
816641812328775684,apr 1  2014 / 4:23 bill warner phd : prayers for kafirs,not_hate,,,,,"[{'bill warner': 'PER'}, {'kafirs': 'MISC'}]"
906759680340328448,are europeans being replaced ? this is a british school in 2017 . find the white kid ..,not_hate,,,,,"[{'europeans': 'MISC'}, {'british': 'MISC'}, {'white kid': 'MISC'}]"
930251039420420097,are we actually fighting an asymmetrical war against white genocide or are we just playing tiddlywinks with enemies who mean to kill us ?,implicit_hate,People of color,People of color want to kill white people,white_grievance,,[]
892862795523411968,are you jewish ? if so you aren't white . either way you're anti-white .,implicit_hate,Jewish people,Jewish people hate white people.,white_grievance,,[{'jewish': 'MISC'}]
847194896360493056,arsonist destroys church recently purchased by white pioneer craig cobb #swrm #whitegenocide #wp via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'craig cobb': 'PER'}, {'whitegenocide': 'ORG'}]"
926155421819265024,as an ex-member of identity evropa  i will not promote that group . i will not bash them either  but my,not_hate,,,,,[{'identity evropa': 'ORG'}]
833834913044557824,as bad as he is i really don't think we should be accusing milo of anything without evidence . its just not right .,not_hate,,,,,[{'milo': 'PER'}]
861742477115625472,as far as cuck knight your probably right  he was an instigator,not_hate,,,,,[{'cuck knight': 'PER'}]
901289102775025668,assuming a low median iq  large population size would still yield an elite .,not_hate,,,,,[]
917594619139035136,attached pic is white sabotage,not_hate,,,,,[]
827003709297078273,ban white male terrorists !,not_hate,,,,,[]
632682513878548480,basic human rightswhat for so how are u guys on jews and blacksben n i hate them,implicit_hate,jews,jews and blacksben n i hate them,incitement,,[{'jews': 'MISC'}]
711545343989694464,because europeans are white like africans are black and asia is asian .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'europeans': 'MISC'}, {'africans': 'MISC'}, {'asia': 'LOC'}, {'asian': 'MISC'}]"
894257377918234624,because i love the diversity & contribution of various cultures . id hate living in a white society,not_hate,,,,,[]
891733270706126850,because it's a white identitarian group .,not_hate,,,,,[]
551110655772590080,because of course #whitepeople need #billboard #marketing kkk #kkk,implicit_hate,Whites,Whites have special privilege.,incitement,,[]
846468756050235392,because of those racist white people  duh . every question has the same answer mr . wallace,explicit_hate,,,,,[{'wallace': 'PER'}]
903033559950270464,because white nationalists  the kkk  and neo-nazis don't have a history of violent intimidation and terrorism in the us .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'kkk': 'ORG'}, {'neo': 'MISC'}, {'nazis': 'MISC'}, {'us': 'LOC'}]"
901262578168598530,because you are not white semite,not_hate,,,,,[]
772057469543706624,beck is alt right . that is he's the alternative to being right .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'beck': 'PER'}, {'alt': 'MISC'}]"
693160492924276737,before i read it was white pride i was going to suggest white only sessions,implicit_hate,White people,White people are superior to people of color,incitement,,[]
280693571328286720,before rushing to judgment  please see our faq page : #freedom #peace #truth #workingclass,not_hate,,,,,[]
910396504627654657,being white is not the original sinracist : magic silencing word whose powers have worn off . white ppl are tired of being called evil 24/7 .,not_hate,,,,,[]
702326068745736192,belgium : non-white invader rapes white woman after dont rape course : via,implicit_hate,Non-whites,Non-whites rape whites,stereotypical,,[{'belgium': 'LOC'}]
881666489689882624,bernie sanders was unavailable for comment .,not_hate,,,,,[{'bernie sanders': 'PER'}]
291090906801635329,best screenplay golden globes : quentin tarantino wins for django unchained | american renaissance,not_hate,,,,,"[{'golden globe': 'MISC'}, {'quentin tarantino': 'PER'}, {'django unchained': 'MISC'}, {'american renaissance': 'MISC'}]"
932790084201480193,bingo they act like they cannot tell the difference between a white supremacist and a white extremist extremist are very few supremacist are very many,not_hate,,,,,[]
872023282198990849,black celebrities who belong to 5 % er anti-white race war cult #swrm via,not_hate,,,,,[]
543182706692337665,black officers torn between duty and race | american renaissance,not_hate,,,,,[{'american renaissance': 'MISC'}]
444733236422647808,black spree shooter wanted to kill as many white people as possible via,not_hate,,,,,[{'black sp': 'MISC'}]
891548140632801280,blonde white women aren't the only type of white women,not_hate,,,,,[]
880504695483236352,boston holocaust museum vandalized arrest made the forward,not_hate,,,,,"[{'boston': 'LOC'}, {'holocaust museum': 'ORG'}]"
901913684284452864,both north america and europe belong to us . white men conquered and colonized both .,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are unaccomplished,incitement,,"[{'north america': 'LOC'}, {'europe': 'LOC'}, {'us': 'LOC'}]"
710127431546306561,breaking : obama to nominate merrick garland to supreme court #scotusnominee,not_hate,,,,,"[{'obama': 'PER'}, {'merrick garland': 'PER'}, {'supreme court': 'ORG'}, {'scotusnominee': 'ORG'}]"
880157203629527040,breaking : ohio dismemberment abortion ban clears ohio senate ! #prolife #theyfeelpain,implicit_hate,,,,,"[{'ohio': 'LOC'}, {'ohio': 'LOC'}, {'senate': 'ORG'}, {'prolife': 'ORG'}, {'theyelpa': 'ORG'}]"
402474559539912704,britain sees race war brewing between non-white invaders | read more :,implicit_hate,"People of color, immigrants","People of color, immigrants are invading Britain and beginning a race war",stereotypical,,[{'britain': 'LOC'}]
908106879313870849,build the dreams of american people first ! ! !,not_hate,,,,,[{'american': 'MISC'}]
873667554514014211,but apparently a safe space for racist  white children is applauded,not_hate,,,,,[]
860651361628807168,but hey  if you really are antifa  90 % + of your friends are white  so you wouldn't really know,not_hate,,,,,[]
855643714399686656,but still mostly white . what about the people buying the politicians ? even more white .,not_hate,,,,,[]
485036483808489473,but their american experience can be used in their home country better,not_hate,,,,,[{'american': 'MISC'}]
809940071046467584,can democrats win back the white working class ? via,not_hate,,,,,[{'democrats': 'MISC'}]
856920748988018690,can i join ur clan,not_hate,,,,,[{'ur': 'ORG'}]
741348577604046853,can whites have black artists shoved down their throats without losing their own culture and heritage ?,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people want to destroy white culture,white_grievance,,[]
897557433333239808,can you describe exactly what sneak attack was ? antifa hitting w / baseball bats ? throwing stuff ? punching ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
925452997357907971,canadian music festival says sorry for racist white staffer who didnt want to move to the back,not_hate,,,,,[{'canadian music festival': 'MISC'}]
137953441690566657,caught on camera : 10 violent #police assaults on #ows protesters #occupywallstwhen will white america fight back ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'occupy': 'ORG'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
394919687743483904,check out this article from : the battle for marriage is not over ! ! !,not_hate,,,,,[]
795951596244910080,chief of army staff  chief of naval staff  vice chief of air staff and the national security advisor met the prime minister .,not_hate,,,,,[]
932785056950702080,chillin my cuz  how you other than spreadin hate  victimhood and dependence on your folks ? really dawg  change your game up a little  promote hope  harmony and a can do attitude rather than the only reason you can't succeed is cause of white cats #novelconcept,not_hate,,,,,[]
785266394841616384,christianity is to be lived in public - in all that we say and do . to get rid of it  evildoers must eliminate us all .,not_hate,,,,,[{'christianity': 'MISC'}]
921396928063029248,classical music  hvy metal / progrock  low crime  space / scientific etc exploration  idealism  education  gun subculture  christian heritage,not_hate,,,,,[]
926015461690667008,come home  white man . rise up against the jewish agenda . join today . you owe it to your race . you owe it to your children . #heil,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'jewish': 'MISC'}, {'heil': 'PER'}]"
619204021115596800,come together white people or perish,implicit_hate,white people,White people need to stick together.,incitement,,[]
905589328377761792,common figure around the conservatism circles,not_hate,,,,,[]
829534589634887680,compared to 2010 there are more white crimes against others than black crimes . pick up a textbook .,not_hate,,,,,[]
666830006404964352,complete idiot john kerry not surprised isis had capabilities to carry out paris attacks .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'john kerry': 'PER'}, {'isis': 'ORG'}, {'paris': 'LOC'}]"
706256595181637632,congrats to #cruzcrew for winning kansas  but you are underperforming huckabee and santorum with evangelicals,not_hate,,,,,"[{'cruzcrew': 'PER'}, {'kansas': 'LOC'}, {'huckabee': 'PER'}, {'santorum': 'PER'}]"
405399853045272576,congrats to my friends at and at for the cert grants today ! hoping for a big religious liberties win !,not_hate,,,,,[]
928316804019249153,correct . so we have to likewise use emotional appeal to frighten our people into choosing sides  ultimately .,not_hate,,,,,[]
727923701249794048,count down until your vile ministry gives up hating transgender and moves on to your next innocent  free victims . hahah,not_hate,,,,,[]
626938792423911424,crooked cops posted movie  take shelter  showing #endtmes visions as mental illness on my youtube feed,not_hate,,,,,[]
706252267377135616,cruz is winning with the exact same percentage as santorum in 2012 . where is president santorum ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'cruz': 'PER'}, {'santorum': 'PER'}, {'santorum': 'PER'}]"
723370269222424576,cruz said kasich should leave because he couldn't get to 1237 . now he can't get to 1237 . drop out lyin ' ted .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'cruz': 'PER'}, {'kasich': 'PER'}, {'ted': 'PER'}]"
728611729752526848,cuck : a white church no more,explicit_hate,,,,,[{'cu': 'ORG'}]
785974946988187648,cucks ? they are democrat plants !,implicit_hate,Democrats,Democrats are conniving and dishonest.,,,[{'democrat': 'MISC'}]
693663334332108801,cuckservatives : becktown : i've been saying for years its coming,not_hate,,,,,"[{'cu': 'ORG'}, {'beck': 'PER'}, {'##town': 'LOC'}]"
938245996840177670,cuckservatives : ben sasse calls out jeff flake,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'cu': 'ORG'}, {'ben sasse': 'PER'}, {'jeff flake': 'PER'}]"
900777960243843073,cultural marxism is a phrase invented by people who have never read marx and don't understand marxism .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'marx': 'MISC'}, {'marxism': 'MISC'}]"
489130532404355072,democrats promote womens health bill for abortion without limits until birth via,not_hate,,,,,[{'democrats': 'MISC'}]
906909246910066691,destruction of culture / less cultural influence and more state control over the economy is lw .,not_hate,,,,,[]
827539907887394817,developing = > milo yiannopoulos to attend friday's white house press briefing,not_hate,,,,,"[{'milo yiannopoulos': 'PER'}, {'white house': 'LOC'}]"
897362340336762882,did you ever really believe he was pro-white ?,implicit_hate,,,,,[{'white': 'MISC'}]
798479148515635200,dismiss fin secretary for fooling you mr pm on his ability to handle the matter pl resign,not_hate,,,,,[{'fin': 'ORG'}]
684995720668180484,do you want more  or less  liberty  welfare & peace for the future ? . the choice is now.rt . follow . #shariafree2016,not_hate,,,,,[{'sharia': 'MISC'}]
653943876831592448,don't tell bernie ; hescandinavian socialism & will shudder islam invasion,implicit_hate,Liberals,Liberals want to allow Muslims to invade the country,stereotypical,,"[{'bernie': 'PER'}, {'hescandinavian': 'MISC'}, {'islam': 'MISC'}]"
909068444150239232,don't think the white public won't turn against the blm unless the lying media tells them to . the white public rejects the media,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people are dangerous,incitement,,[{'blm': 'ORG'}]
829716325429817345,don't worry  bill . it's not a pogrom . we're just replacing jews with white people .,implicit_hate,jews,replacing jews with white people,white_grievance,,"[{'bill': 'PER'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}]"
847895153020989446,dough boy fattass is a cuck  what a shock,implicit_hate,fat men,fat men are not masculine,,,[{'##tas': 'PER'}]
519631405433638913,dr . david duke : will the white race survive ? ( video ) va #whitepride,not_hate,,,,,"[{'david duke': 'PER'}, {'white': 'MISC'}, {'va': 'ORG'}, {'whitepride': 'ORG'}]"
615247096162205697,e . g .  white supremacist asks black xian bakery owner for anti-xian racist cake . liberty = denial . rt ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'xian': 'MISC'}, {'anti': 'MISC'}, {'xian': 'MISC'}]"
834167933236555780,elin krantz : just another #dead white liberal #female #raped to #death by #non-white #invader via,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are rapists,stereotypical,,[{'elin krantz': 'PER'}]
906845049215787014,even when not elected  hinduism was the guiding principle of india  even m k gandhi wanted rule of lord rama,not_hate,,,,,"[{'hinduism': 'MISC'}, {'india': 'LOC'}, {'m k gandhi': 'PER'}, {'lord': 'PER'}, {'rama': 'PER'}]"
713389967985086464,even white muslims ? ?,not_hate,,,,,[{'muslims': 'MISC'}]
897227753048522752,every statue they take wakes more people upthis cult will not stop  always finding a str,not_hate,,,,,[]
801186977001324544,every white christian or not should know about russian jew communists ; prior to ww white hollocaust vs herrel,not_hate,,,,,"[{'christian': 'MISC'}, {'russian jew': 'MISC'}, {'white hollocaust': 'PER'}, {'herrel': 'PER'}]"
935277194103939073,everything is racist .,not_hate,,,,,[]
764615629311664128,exactly ! all of a sudden in 2015  he's now a racist ! give me a break ! !,not_hate,,,,,[]
861830818741628928,exactly . if i were a leftist / antifa i would be trying to fracture the rw ' street ' coal,not_hate,,,,,[{'rw': 'ORG'}]
677521472995401729,expose ashish khetan today . he has wrongly quoted the govt letter : sambit patra  bjp #arvindcricketcard,not_hate,,,,,"[{'ashish khetan': 'PER'}, {'govt': 'ORG'}, {'sambit patra bjp': 'ORG'}, {'arvindcricket': 'ORG'}]"
923934799005409281,exposing the hatred towards whites is good ... people need to see it even if they are scared to react .,not_hate,,,,,[]
846804703254073344,extinction of america's white population speeds up #swrm #whitegenocide #prowhite #speedsup via,implicit_hate,People of color,People of color what white people to go away and take over America,white_grievance,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
301531636472889344,fair . most of us know you're a racist hate group . so stfu .,not_hate,,,,,[]
920285506503618560,fair immigration is a branded hate group whose members are racists and white supremacists .,not_hate,,,,,[{'fair immigration': 'ORG'}]
849017222328668160,fake news for sure . face the reality ! open your eyes . you cannot change the past .,not_hate,,,,,[]
645689837417201664,family of shitskin ingrates tries to put one over white america  gullible status-whoring white via,explicit_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
804696003165192193,fetal tissue panel recommends prosecution for planned parenthood : . #ppsellsbabyparts,not_hate,,,,,[{'planned parenthood': 'ORG'}]
756576188890550273,final solution : the 1941 plan to exterminate germans #whitegenocide #munich #prayformunich,implicit_hate,Jewish people,Jewish people wanted to eradicate the Germans,white_grievance,,"[{'germans': 'MISC'}, {'whitegenocide': 'ORG'}, {'munich': 'LOC'}, {'prayformunich': 'ORG'}]"
461163325112332289,fishy holohoax : jews drowned in the bug river ( nov . 1942 ): jews not gassed ( or electrocuted or steamed to deat ...,explicit_hate,,,,,[{'bug': 'LOC'}]
899800175639769088,for only one pair of legs a day you can give poor afghanie people freedom even if they don't want it .,not_hate,,,,,[{'afghanie': 'MISC'}]
835244282952953861,french people are white . that doesn't mean they don't have rights .,not_hate,,,,,[{'french': 'MISC'}]
833022318846767106,from a planned anti-trump walkout to a milo keynote--cpac has come a long way in a year .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'anti': 'MISC'}, {'trump': 'MISC'}, {'milo': 'ORG'}, {'cpac': 'ORG'}]"
938119145627021312,furthermore everything you accuse the white race of has been comitted by every other race imagineable . slavery was around long before and we were the only race to put and end to it . you know nothing but old talking points someone told you to memorize . youre fumbling in ignorance .,not_hate,,,,,[]
872170791466565632,german #holocaust #revisionist patriot horst mahler arrested in hungary via,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are liars,stereotypical,,"[{'german': 'MISC'}, {'holocaust': 'MISC'}, {'horst mahler': 'PER'}, {'hungary': 'LOC'}]"
921081994624294917,given how moderate & reasonable richard & mike were at the press conference  white students are now in an awkward position . #togetheruf,not_hate,,,,,"[{'richard': 'PER'}, {'mike': 'PER'}, {'together': 'ORG'}]"
901545109296218112,good to see infowars coming to the defense of - wait for it -  one of america's most prominent white supremacist groups .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'infowar': 'ORG'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
913906780375273473,great thread . what optics are you proposing as alternative ? either way  better to run an experiment and,not_hate,,,,,[]
712627109672263680,great to see all the support for #religiousfreedom ! #letthemserve #littlesisters,not_hate,,,,,"[{'##msve': 'ORG'}, {'littlesisters': 'ORG'}]"
170583343946153984,great video  please share . #jews are indeed guilty of white #genocide #zionism #zog #whitepride,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'jews': 'MISC'}, {'zion': 'MISC'}]"
721017454034624512,growing ? or white flight from other citiies ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
904843221003468800,halal also means the animals were killed in the most gruesome manner ... a manner that is not permitted in most jurisdictions except for islam,not_hate,,,,,"[{'hal': 'MISC'}, {'islam': 'LOC'}]"
920339777706188806,has a white supremacy problem : analysis shows supporters of family research council embrace white supremacy,not_hate,,,,,"[{'white': 'MISC'}, {'family research council': 'ORG'}, {'white': 'MISC'}]"
287370711889240064,has the white race become too lazy ? our people have largely fallen to the disease of #materialism & comfort ... #news,implicit_hate,White people,White people are lazy and diseased,,,[]
908371865114234881,hate group because your proud to be a white american christian ? insanity ! and very disappointing !,implicit_hate,White people,White people who are proud to be white are hateful,white_grievance,,[{'american christian': 'MISC'}]
620615120297795584,have you ever been such a degenerate that your only accomplishment is being white,not_hate,,,,,[]
934252176846835712,he is also a black racist . dont forget that .,implicit_hate,black people,black people are racist.,white_grievance,,[]
833572524134916097,he is more new-right than alt-right . he is just a gimmick to divide even more,not_hate,,,,,[{'new': 'MISC'}]
925593017343512577,he overdosed on black pills when the narrative was hijacked in charlottesville .,implicit_hate,Black people,Black people use too many drugs,,,[{'charlottesville': 'LOC'}]
938913165772865536,he really seems to be a racist,not_hate,,,,,[]
928344833449656320,he should be fired for virtue signaling like a cuck before any evidence was out . how can a man like that lead soldiers,implicit_hate,Conservative men,Conservative men are weak and feminine,,,[]
917841301688737794,he was with a group of people all looking for trouble .,not_hate,,,,,[]
827364099893911552,he's a gay jew . not a white supremacist,not_hate,,,,,"[{'gay jew': 'MISC'}, {'white supre': 'MISC'}]"
885689843141025792,heartiste is anti white .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'heart': 'PER'}, {'##iste': 'ORG'}]"
712471191437516801,heidi cruz : goldman sachs banker  council on foreign relations member  open borders globalist via yup,not_hate,,,,,"[{'heidi cruz': 'PER'}, {'goldman sachs banker council on foreign relations': 'ORG'}, {'open borders globalist': 'ORG'}]"
800090249653317632,hello  brother ! i am new to twitter ... is there anyway we could get in contact ?,not_hate,,,,,[{'twitter': 'ORG'}]
933450079012257792,help us in california . they are killing americans jobs and taking over the state . some wont go out if they dont have to . a lot dont speak english . they have taken over everything . the politicians are not for americans . they are for illegals . cant move,implicit_hate,immigrants,Immigrants take jobs away from Americans.,stereotypical,,"[{'california': 'LOC'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}, {'english': 'MISC'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}]"
938296048971378688,here is what u need to know two semites attacking white women for standing up,not_hate,,,,,[{'semi': 'MISC'}]
942856631653687296,heretics = infidels halal to kill,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims want to kill.,stereotypical,,[]
552793810745700352,hey guys ... i'm not mexican can yall shout me out ? ? ? i'm trying to get my rap name out there and i have a black friend who raps,not_hate,,,,,[{'mexican': 'MISC'}]
736677045195788288,hey there is a new way to be racist,not_hate,,,,,[]
539949474039480320,hi do you have to be white to join,not_hate,,,,,[]
797699795997454336,hi one more example of govt official harassing a common man for tax erosion . modi govt . is questioning termites too,not_hate,,,,,[{'modi': 'ORG'}]
593016153200529409,hi white  t-shirtz & hoodies are named by you ! click now ! : . ciao,not_hate,,,,,[]
775699707054153728,highlights from #vvs16 #valuesvotersummit from what a great week !,not_hate,,,,,[{'what a': 'MISC'}]
758060720403652608,hillary strategist blames stupid white people for popularity of trump via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'hillary': 'PER'}, {'trump': 'PER'}]"
767854094115561472,hillary's amnesty plan is treason  she is a traitor,not_hate,,,,,[{'hillary': 'PER'}]
892591877467381761,his white half is just as bad,implicit_hate,White people,White people are bad and being even half white is bad,,,[]
345719353322393600,hope he takes them to court . overstepping boundaries .,not_hate,,,,,[]
430533369454022656,horrible . 9 year old white boy commits suicide after being tormented for months by racist arabs via,implicit_hate,Arabs,Arabs are evil and hate white people,stereotypical,,[{'arabs': 'MISC'}]
828736331182379009,how dare you refer to his religion . racist ! !,not_hate,,,,,[]
933018235083083777,how did you miss the point and be wrong at the same time ? what takeover ? no one said anything about that and white people kill each other too linda,not_hate,,,,,[]
685190832366981121,how does stealing women's health options lead to a victory for women ? incomprehensible,not_hate,,,,,[]
939586791522340866,how rich did that racist get  what a racket !,not_hate,,,,,[]
896931866623713280,how this black man sees all white people,not_hate,,,,,[]
746311923138965504,howie-baby  we are going to make a white race kingdom  no jews allowed !,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'howie': 'PER'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}]"
809239947446276102,hufpo is now labeling an ' anti-muslim hate group ' i wonder what they call groups who hate america ? heroes ?,not_hate,,,,,"[{'hufpo': 'ORG'}, {'muslim': 'MISC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
648966705012543488,i bet you hate muslims too  typical racist conservative .,not_hate,,,,,[{'muslims': 'MISC'}]
660726934586961920,i brought breakfast for you  yes we are legion,not_hate,,,,,[]
886703640572030976,i cant bring myself to be friends with white people who dont hate being white and want to be in charge of their own country .,not_hate,,,,,[]
636999194616680449,i didn't call his a democratic gay black racist  did you ? !,not_hate,,,,,[{'democratic': 'MISC'}]
881719182827454465,i don't hate you . i white guys .,not_hate,,,,,[]
822819729836490753,i don't think his message of racial inclusion was aimed at minorities . i think it was aimed at cucky whites .,implicit_hate,White people,White people are not racially inclusive,white_grievance,,[]
920444349263044610,i don't view any as naturally inferior  we can't really tell in the small period of our lives . you however by positing that the white race ..,not_hate,,,,,[]
919631076548517889,i don't want any murders illegal or citizen . but there seems to be a disproportionate amount of focus on people that are not the real danger,not_hate,,,,,[]
753641342249697281,i employ many people in the state of virginia - jobs  jobs  jobs ! crooked hillary will sell us out  just like her husband did with nafta .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'virginia': 'LOC'}, {'hillary': 'PER'}, {'nafta': 'PER'}]"
917807097663885312,i guarantee they're scrambling in charlottesville to get this arrest warrant overturned or canceled .,not_hate,,,,,[{'charlottesville': 'LOC'}]
933546582460465154,i have an ultra liberal next door who says there is no such thing as black racist only white people can be racist unbelievable,implicit_hate,white people,White people are racist.,,,[]
942896526522757120,i heard twitter is cracking down on white supremacists . are they also cracking down on racist blacks calling for th,implicit_hate,White people,Twitter is cracking down White supremacists,,,[]
910545145812127745,i hope they're ready to get primaried by people who are willing to do so .,not_hate,,,,,[]
928425960252289025,i know it did . but there's no way of knowing whether or not the people involved from the beginning were already trs listeners . given how popular flyers are by folks from and  it wouldn't be surprising at all  really .,not_hate,,,,,[{'trs': 'ORG'}]
794497389524439040,i know you love america not god but you don't want a communist in the white house . they will destroy our life,not_hate,,,,,"[{'america': 'LOC'}, {'god': 'PER'}, {'communist': 'MISC'}, {'white house': 'LOC'}]"
834329032644763649,i liked some of what milo did  although i hated him for plenty of things .,not_hate,,,,,[{'milo': 'PER'}]
916448107113705472,i live in texas  but despite being a gop wonderland  white people continue to murder and rape and steal . never trust whitey . violent race .,implicit_hate,White people,White people are violent criminals,,,"[{'texas': 'LOC'}, {'go': 'MISC'}, {'whitey': 'PER'}]"
916495886930317313,i lived there it was fine you are just a scared white dude,implicit_hate,White people,White people are afraid,,,[]
897195637397229569,i love it ! the media needs to stop saying that every black loves obama  every woman loves hillary  and every white for trump is racist .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'obama': 'PER'}, {'hillary': 'PER'}, {'trump': 'PER'}]"
301177217776492548,i might shock a few people saying this being a nationalist but you can't take the klan serious,not_hate,,,,,[{'klan': 'MISC'}]
901198947749949440,i see that you might protect monuments and lead people to hate antifa  msm  and leftists ge,not_hate,,,,,[{'ms': 'MISC'}]
897097524170850304,i stick up for white people  thats not what you're are racist and putting down other races .,implicit_hate,White people,White people puts down other races,white_grievance,,[]
900343390121861120,i support the alt right aspersions for portion of us to be all white ethnostate  even,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people should segregate,incitement,,[{'alt right': 'ORG'}]
838062389115437057,i support the white brotherhood,implicit_hate,white people,White people are superior.,incitement,,[{'white brotherhood': 'ORG'}]
911826525493747712,i take that back . one of his parents must be white . not purebred,implicit_hate,People of color,"People of color are inferior to white people, even if one of their parents is white",inferiority,,[]
942771524641198080,i think he meant white nationalists are free of thought .,not_hate,,,,,[]
894281139296325632,i think we'll be facing some young  well-trained antifa as well . heads up .,not_hate,,,,,[{'anti': 'ORG'}]
866433995810254849,i thought with statues gone people would sing and hold hands under a rainbow . are you saying racism still exists ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
829403686958989314,i used to live on se university ! i wish these fliers were around a year ago when i was still there . great work !,not_hate,,,,,[{'se university': 'ORG'}]
933184189716766720,i very much doubt you are white person of european descent . from,implicit_hate,People of color,People of color pretend to be white,,,[{'european': 'MISC'}]
456140466254118912,i want to ask hindus ? any comments ? ..,not_hate,,,,,[{'hindus': 'MISC'}]
901260614521114625,i was born white  i can't help it . i should just kill myself ... said no one ever .,implicit_hate,Minorities,Minorities are racist,white_grievance,,[]
896556218281582592,i would say not the beginning but a nice warm up liberals you want a cultural war so today you got a small taste of it,not_hate,,,,,[]
804303647211393024,i'm black not white !,not_hate,,,,,[]
945105296757637120,i'm going to assume you live in a sizable city . most of the white there are liberals and are no doubt the reason you think that .,not_hate,,,,,[]
893539806197800960,i'm not sure #antifa ever knows how they intend to do anything . let's just appreciate the entertainment .,not_hate,,,,,[{'antifa': 'ORG'}]
884143354358882305,i'm talking ' american ' white not european white,not_hate,,,,,"[{'american': 'MISC'}, {'european': 'MISC'}]"
833124632265793536,i'm thinking there are some good people in that movement but it's been hijacked . this guy's an embarrassment .,not_hate,,,,,[]
922107855607607296,i'm white  southern  and proud ! !,not_hate,,,,,[{'white southern': 'MISC'}]
937762750591315969,i've been watching the women issue play out in the alt-right . my take is that it is another reason why online movements don't work . in real life  these issues tend to sort out,not_hate,,,,,[{'alt': 'MISC'}]
938287088704917509,i've seen a lot of stuff that i disagree with including some comments which are crazy . the typical woman isn't an e-celeb that thirsty men gawk at like tomi lahren,not_hate,,,,,[{'tomi lahren': 'PER'}]
846377588381634561,iceland is a lily white ethnostate compared to sweden,not_hate,,,,,"[{'iceland': 'LOC'}, {'sweden': 'LOC'}]"
407539663960682496,idk > graphic > mandela's rainbow nation : white woman raped then stoned by racist blacks ( video ) via,not_hate,,,,,"[{'id': 'ORG'}, {'mandela': 'PER'}, {'rainbow nation': 'ORG'}]"
926977658608500736,if a muslim kill a jew they celebrate him as a hero . if a christian kill a jew we call,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are killers.,stereotypical,,"[{'muslim': 'MISC'}, {'jew': 'MISC'}, {'christian': 'MISC'}, {'jew': 'MISC'}]"
907417515269267457,if it's white it's right,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are wrong,incitement,,[]
827171940481826816,if milo provokes to shutdown federal funds to berkeley  i will be cool with him . he will deserve enormous credit for that,not_hate,,,,,"[{'milo': 'PER'}, {'berkeley': 'LOC'}]"
476881017869832192,if only we'd realize it's just #clowardandpiven of dear leader obama we'd be taking a stand as americans .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'obama': 'PER'}, {'americans': 'MISC'}]"
892913710154514432,if so  i'll join you . i'm not nor are you a racist we just want corruption by obama recognized and punishable by the law .,not_hate,,,,,[{'obama': 'PER'}]
905878327411474433,if the dogs and flowers are white .. shut it down,not_hate,,,,,[]
938105223217860608,if the supreme court sides with the business  then we will be heading in a bad di,not_hate,,,,,[{'supreme court': 'ORG'}]
924429796435812352,if the whites who condemn us get their way america will look like detroit and india ! does that sound good to you !,implicit_hate,White people,White people want others to live in poverty.,,,"[{'america': 'LOC'}, {'detroit': 'LOC'}, {'india': 'LOC'}]"
857050526575456256,if they're not the answer  what is ? do the people have to stand up ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
562176015791706113,if what you are saying is true what stops nda govt to arrest kejriwal ? its not upa anymore  they are in power,not_hate,,,,,"[{'nda': 'ORG'}, {'kejriwal': 'PER'}, {'upa': 'ORG'}]"
848073262777106436,if you also think white heritage is hate  would you feel comfortable living in a country with zero white heritage ? be honest .,not_hate,,,,,[]
421432329853472768,if you re-branded yourself a jihadist psychopath we might just let you in .,not_hate,,,,,[]
776538501798060032,if you're not scandinavian or irish you're not white .,implicit_hate,White people,White people are racist against other white people,,,"[{'scandinavian': 'MISC'}, {'irish': 'MISC'}]"
904543441115283457,illegal aliens should be suing in a mexican court  with a mexican attorney  in mexico . they have no rights in america . they are illegal .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'mexican': 'MISC'}, {'mexican': 'MISC'}, {'mexico': 'LOC'}, {'america': 'LOC'}]"
901175786992017408,illinois gop governor wants to make illinois a sanctuary state !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'illinois': 'LOC'}, {'illinois': 'LOC'}]"
582003763310907392,im new to twitter and glad to see so many following a great page like yours . i wish to also spread truth about national socialism,not_hate,,,,,[]
921508801437724674,immigration is an opt-in regime . the people that come here want to be a part of the project . they already see the value in the system that's in place . that's what i think anti-immigration activists fail to realize .,not_hate,,,,,[]
662077607286992896,in 14 hours  1000 kkk members will be outed . expect us   and more .,not_hate,,,,,[{'kkk': 'ORG'}]
859592471046696962,in england  you had the white flower girls that would give men dressed in civies white flowers of cowardice .,not_hate,,,,,[{'england': 'LOC'}]
946093278763606017,in stunning black and white technicolor ! =d,not_hate,,,,,[]
923389501883539458,in the old days of america baptists were stereotyped as either being white trash or blacks .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'america': 'LOC'}, {'baptist': 'MISC'}]"
662536462978514945,indian intellectuals bemoan everything . they are like rudali-s  professional mourners ; these intellectuals mourn all the time . 3 / n,implicit_hate,Indian people,Indian people whine too much,,,"[{'indian': 'MISC'}, {'rudali': 'PER'}]"
779323113309896705,infanticide is unacceptable in a civilized society . congress must pass the born-alive abortion survivors protection act .,implicit_hate,Liberals,Liberals are baby murderers,,,"[{'congress': 'ORG'}, {'survivors protection act': 'MISC'}]"
847637101638148096,infrastructure is the white mans game .,implicit_hate,white people,white people exclude others,,,[{'white mans': 'MISC'}]
835203929625460736,inspiring estonian nationalist torch light march . thousands marched in support of nationalism . #estonia,not_hate,,,,,"[{'estonian': 'MISC'}, {'estonia': 'LOC'}]"
251020358331801601,insulting a religion is not racism . its bigotry . racism is hating a race . hence racist .,not_hate,,,,,[]
656549117561348096,intends to score house reconciliation act . it's time to #defundpp #prolife via,not_hate,,,,,[{'house reconciliation act': 'MISC'}]
776294612298194944,international jew criminal plot afoot 2wipe out white race !,explicit_hate,,,,,[{'international jew': 'MISC'}]
336579772731768832,interracial marriage = white genocide,implicit_hate,People of color,People of color are trying to get rid of white people by marrying into white families,white_grievance,,[{'white': 'MISC'}]
273881306583166977,ireland : wrong to blame pro-life catholics for savita's death,not_hate,,,,,"[{'ireland': 'LOC'}, {'savita': 'PER'}]"
900504511135047681,is a white supremacist,not_hate,,,,,[{'white supre': 'MISC'}]
461527506407796736,is adult abortion ok ? oklahoma's botched lethal injection starts new front in battle over executions,not_hate,,,,,[{'oklahoma': 'LOC'}]
877965399186444288,is choosing the path of legacy media and will decline as a result .,not_hate,,,,,[]
932426001921007616,is the head of the suspected black supremacist group . has to make multi accounts to spread his hate for white folks just like kkk,not_hate,,,,,[{'kkk': 'ORG'}]
590718234099372032,is white nationalism an #adl honey pot front ?,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are devious,white_grievance,,"[{'white': 'MISC'}, {'adl': 'ORG'}]"
610244283300384768,isis threatens pam geller  jihad threat against the white house,not_hate,,,,,"[{'isis': 'ORG'}, {'pam geller': 'PER'}, {'white house': 'LOC'}]"
845587073104994304,islam is racist,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are racist,stereotypical,,[{'islam': 'MISC'}]
934832585716518912,islams hate  wrapped in western goodness .,not_hate,,,,,"[{'islam': 'MISC'}, {'western': 'MISC'}]"
729756649079066624,isn't high corporate taxes + high income taxes + regulations + free-trade the formula of deindustrialization ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
898951403481288705,isn't it crazy how people turn a blind-eye to present day slavery and instead  would rather focus on slavery from 400yrs ago ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
940426630413062146,isn't that how it usually begins ? this hatred for infidels and belief in islamic supremacy etc .,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims hate people who are not Muslim,stereotypical,,[{'islamic': 'MISC'}]
315653606873370624,isn't your wife white ?,not_hate,,,,,[]
486567996979040256,israel prepares for #myjihad islam muslims bjp modi #ramzan tmc mps #femen #tcot iraq isis syria,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims are violent and want to overthrow Israel,,,"[{'israel': 'LOC'}, {'myjihad islam muslims': 'ORG'}, {'bjp': 'ORG'}, {'modi': 'ORG'}, {'ramzan tmc': 'ORG'}, {'femen': 'ORG'}, {'tc': 'ORG'}, {'iraq': 'LOC'}, {'syria': 'LOC'}]"
696190024811827200,it is driven by jews  carried out by somalis and arabs . the issue is keeping europe white .,explicit_hate,,,,,"[{'jews': 'MISC'}, {'somali': 'MISC'}, {'arabs': 'MISC'}, {'europe': 'LOC'}]"
892142996610830336,it is not racist and you are not a hate group if you believe in following federal immigration law . #commonsense #illegalimmigration,not_hate,,,,,[]
892603537049309189,it makes you honest  not racist .,not_hate,,,,,[]
820308577495744512,it seems atheists are intent upon stealing away our freedom of religion ...,implicit_hate,Atheists,Atheists don't believe in religious freedom.,,,[]
926995908981538816,it was founded by john tanton  an open white supremacist  whose goal is to maintain a majority white population 2 /,not_hate,,,,,"[{'john tanton': 'PER'}, {'supremac': 'MISC'}]"
891108622650003458,it would be everything fine if the cop was christian or jew . only they can kill in se,implicit_hate,"Christians, Jews",Christians and Jews can get away with murder in the southeast,,,"[{'christian': 'MISC'}, {'jew': 'MISC'}]"
904945183938273281,it would be nice .. i would like the idea of my white race surviving .. to thrive and kick a,implicit_hate,white people,White people are superior.,incitement,,[]
896479023483801600,it's also inherently american to allow people their constitutional rights .,not_hate,,,,,[{'american': 'MISC'}]
298983682704801792,it's axiomatic that all southern white men are lousy in bed .,implicit_hate,southern white men,Southern white men are bad in bed.,,,[]
836582871770902528,it's fundamentally different . whites are better off without blacks and jews ; both parasites on white civilization,implicit_hate,Black folks and Jewish folks,Black folks and Jewish folks are parasites on white civilization,inferiority,,"[{'whites': 'MISC'}, {'jews': 'MISC'}]"
922619794523934720,it's gotten worse because white america is waking . we need to keep pushing .,not_hate,,,,,[{'america': 'LOC'}]
924393248780582912,it's not even close to white nationalist .,not_hate,,,,,[]
425049831778709504,it's us white gentiles getting screwed ! :,implicit_hate,white people,White people are disadvantaged.,white_grievance,,[{'##tile': 'MISC'}]
915685988483108864,its 75 % white which is very high when the > 22 population is only about half white,not_hate,,,,,[]
339454048832978944,its not a phobia if the islamic want to kill us ! better to kill them first ! period !,explicit_hate,,,,,[{'islamic': 'MISC'}]
921554247434588160,its ok to love who you are . unless you're white,implicit_hate,white people,white people are inferior,white_grievance,,[]
868871289242517505,jewish activists welcome the scandals slowing the trump agenda,implicit_hate,Jewish activists,Jewish activists cause scandals.,stereotypical,,"[{'jewish': 'MISC'}, {'trump': 'PER'}]"
757798305757663232,jewish man with gun threatens black councilwoman over holocaust museum comments,not_hate,,,,,"[{'jewish': 'MISC'}, {'holocaust': 'MISC'}]"
668843064975233026,jews know deep down  they're not white,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are not white,other,,"[{'jews': 'MISC'}, {'white': 'MISC'}]"
771184340021551106,jews run banking  media  academia  and govt ; you're the dummies .,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews control the world,stereotypical,,[{'jews': 'MISC'}]
830067009543143425,jews want each of those girls to reject white men and use their white wombs to hatch black babies with black men .,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are conniving and racist,inferiority,,[{'jews': 'MISC'}]
453586582558085120,jordan lorence of on . #elanephotography read : what now ? court won't hear gay wedding appeal,not_hate,,,,,"[{'jordan lorence': 'PER'}, {'on': 'ORG'}, {'el': 'ORG'}]"
923371590913585152,just like white nations  white antiquity belongs to all  deconstructed via multilayered pastiche of ethnicities  genders  and classes . / 4,not_hate,,,,,[]
902215776819703808,just look at all those white supremacists helping those they hate down in texas ... ironic  perfect example of the love we have 4 our brothers,not_hate,,,,,"[{'supremac': 'MISC'}, {'texas': 'LOC'}]"
799265200511848448,just search twitter with ' white people '  you'd be surprised on how many anti-white non-whites there are . #diversity,implicit_hate,non-white people,non-white people are racist,white_grievance,,[]
898667357098303488,karma for white supremacy is gonna be great ! ! !,not_hate,,,,,[{'white': 'MISC'}]
924709191943639046,keep debating optics guys . keep arguing over the really really important,not_hate,,,,,[]
940854601393328128,keep pressuring the established party . there is no alternative - and there is no where else white people can go .,not_hate,,,,,[]
442180802692911105,kejriwal actually wants to join bjp  it seems ; he only wants a good deal ! !,not_hate,,,,,"[{'kejriwal': 'PER'}, {'bjp': 'ORG'}]"
428590254962905088,lahore was a beautiful city dominated by sikhs and hindus ... we lost it ...,implicit_hate,Muslims,Muslims banishes Non-Muslims,other,,"[{'lahore': 'LOC'}, {'sikhs': 'MISC'}, {'hindus': 'MISC'}]"
840879046137323522,le pen more popular than socialist candidate among young voters,not_hate,,,,,[{'le pen': 'PER'}]
715696282757533697,less than 72 hours now until gets dropkicked . feeling godly tonight ? #trusted,not_hate,,,,,[]
842534970325458944,let white sas immigrate to us .,not_hate,,,,,[{'white sas': 'ORG'}]
556151549412405248,liars and killer daubed on holocaust memorial day poster : liars and killer daubed on holocaust memoria ...,not_hate,,,,,"[{'holocaust memorial day': 'MISC'}, {'holocaust memoria': 'MISC'}]"
687835401692803072,lindsey looks like he is about to cry #gopdebate,not_hate,,,,,"[{'lindsey': 'PER'}, {'gopdebate': 'MISC'}]"
924418039591899136,literally ! and paid people . and they tried to get people,not_hate,,,,,[]
888869632735629312,lmao sorry,not_hate,,,,,[{'lmao': 'ORG'}]
669417452871262210,lol hitler angry at aamir khan on leaving,not_hate,,,,,"[{'lol hitler': 'PER'}, {'aamir khan': 'PER'}]"
896879424825589760,lol you are a sad little troll ... but who knows i may try white because i have never seen a white person before nor a black for that matter,not_hate,,,,,[{'troll': 'MISC'}]
919309648171356166,lol you support trump but you don't understand how the media lies and smears ppl & groups ? really ? !,not_hate,,,,,[{'trump': 'PER'}]
880932877810237440,lol you're citing business insider ? lol . black on white rape,not_hate,,,,,[]
838080330938650625,lol you're jewish though . not white .,implicit_hate,Jews,Jews are not white,other,,"[{'jewish': 'MISC'}, {'white': 'MISC'}]"
